{
    "subject": "Leonid_Trauberg",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "The_Youth_of_Maxim",
    "human_readable": "Leonid Trauberg created The Youth of Maxim.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8221301436424255,
            "question": "Who created 'The Youth of Maxim'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6403860449790955,
            "question": "When was 'The Youth of Maxim' likely created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5316563844680786,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in 'The Youth of Maxim'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4054912328720093,
            "question": "What kind of story is 'The Youth of Maxim'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39690327644348145,
            "question": "Who are the likely main characters in 'The Youth of Maxim'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36778971552848816,
            "question": "What genre does 'The Youth of Maxim' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34267544746398926,
            "question": "What is the title of the work by Leonid Trauberg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3307230770587921,
            "question": "Is Leonid Trauberg known for writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27784547209739685,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Leonid Trauberg's creative works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25481539964675903,
            "question": "Are there any other works by Leonid Trauberg you know about?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Leonid Trauberg created The Youth of Maxim.",
            "html": "yago_17903_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Leonid Trauberg's creative works?",
            "html": "yago_17903_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Leonid Trauberg known for writing?",
            "html": "yago_17903_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the work by Leonid Trauberg?",
            "html": "yago_17903_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17903_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17903_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17903_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17903_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17903_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17903_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17903_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17903_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17903_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17903_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the response to your query:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents mention that \"Youth of Maxim\" is a 1935 Soviet historical drama film written and directed by Grigori Kozintsev and Leonid Trauberg. This directly supports the statement that Leonid Trauberg created The Youth of Maxim."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support that Grigori Kozintsev and Leonid Trauberg wrote and directed the film \"Youth of Maxim.\" Therefore, the statement that Leonid Trauberg created \"The Youth of Maxim\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}